Hey, here is a quick demo about ScreenSense which is submitted for the Global Engineering Hackathon.
So why and what is ScreenSense?
So, especially me, whenever I browse Chrome, I have a lot of questions, so I take a screenshot of it
and then put it to ChatGPT or Claude and ask basically what it is.
And in this process it takes a lot of time, I take a screenshot and I forget to delete the screenshot
and you know there is a lot of mess and this ScreenSense provides a very unique UI
which comes on top of your existing Chrome and it will be very easy to use as well.
So I will just show you how it is done.
All you have to do is hover the button and then ask anything and you will get your answer right in front of you.
So there is a quick 30 seconds demo on the website you can just watch it and which will also be shown in this video
and basically we are screen-aware, voice-first interaction and we also provide text plus audio or audio only or text only as the user prefers.
And this is one of the unique designs in our current product that is explanation levels.
So that example is also provided in the website that if you want you can try it out.
So basically what is an API?
So it answers a kid level, student level, college, PhD or executive.
So I will personally prefer kid level so it explains me in very detailed and easy way so that I can understand.
So if you want to use this product, all you have to do is clone this GitHub repo first and then I will show you more.
Select the repo that you just cloned and we show you a quick 3-step guide on how to set up this product
where we have to enable the microphone and then a quick show on how this product works and then you launch it and the extension is ready for use.
Before we use the ScreenSense agent, we need to do one last setup.
Click on the extension, go to ScreenSense Voice and then click on settings, then you land on the settings page.
So we have all these other customizable information and then there's this Groq API key and ElevenLabs API key that you need to set.
So both are free, once you create an account you will be given a Groq API key for free and even ElevenLabs.
But there's a catch on ElevenLabs because there's only up to a certain level that you can use it for free and after that you have to pay for it.
So once you do that you can just set it up and you can just use it.
So let's quickly see a demo.
Hey, what does FFN mean here?
FFN stands for Feed Forward Network used in the transformer architecture.
Hey, what are we looking at right now?
We're looking at the MacBook Neo product page on Apple's website, available for pre-order starting March 11th.
And what is this?
It's the Apple Watch Ultra 3, a new smartwatch model priced from $799.
It looks like this has a lot of features. Can you tell me what these are?
The Apple Watch Ultra 3 has various features like different finishes, display, battery and durability.
It also has water resistance and a customizable action button.